<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<postcardexamples>
    <postcard n="1">
        <senderaddress side="b" name="Dorothy-Murray">
            419 Valley Wood Dr, Salisbury, MD, 21001
        </senderaddress>
        <recipientaddress side="b" name="Mr-Mrs. Perry Morgan">
            653 Fairview Av., Westbury, N.Y., 11590
        </recipientaddress>
        <printedheader side="b">
            Holloway Hall Bell Tower
            Salisbury State College Salisbury, Maryland
        </printedheader>
        <printedtext side="b">
            The center section of Holloway Hall at Salisbury State College, including the noble bell tower atop which one can scan the historical city of Salisbury in its entirety, was completed in 1929. Students and townspeople alike are enriched by lyrical sounds emanating from the tower's Carillon of Bells, presented to the College by the Alumni Association on November 5, 1973.
        </printedtext>
        <printedpubinfo side="b">
            Pub. by H. K. Barnett. Allison Park, Pa. 15101
        </printedpubinfo>
        <writtentext side="b">
            <date>Aug. 5</date>Dear Counsins: Pleasant having your company. Next time make it longer so that we can all get out and exploer the peninsula together. Thanks for all the goodies! Am sure you managed to show yourself a good time in Baltimore. Cooled off a mite (degree or 2). Be well, and love, Dorothy-Murray
        </writtentext>
    </postcard>
    <postcard n="2">
        <senderaddress side="b" name="Molly">
            Wilson Av.
        </senderaddress>
        <recipientaddress side="b" name="Mrs. Andrew Perry"/>
        <printedheader side="a">
            Along the water front. Matunuck, R.I.
        </printedheader>
        <printedtext/>
        <printedpubinfo side="b">
            Pub. By The Rhode Island News Company. Providence, R.I.
        </printedpubinfo>
        <writtentext side="b">
            <date/>R.I. Views
        </writtentext>
    </postcard>
    <postcard n="3">
        <senderaddress side="a" name="Esther Manor Executive Office">
            Rt. 17B, Monticello, N.Y., 12701
        </senderaddress>
        <recipientaddress side="a" name="Miss Christina Stetina">
            633 E. 224th Street, Bronx, New York
        </recipientaddress>
        <printedheader side="b">
            Time to pack your tennis racquet, golf clubs, camera, tanning lotion, swim suits, evening attire, anything else you may want -- and your best smile!
        </printedheader>
        <printedtext side="b">
            Dear Friends: It has been a long, cold, snowy winter. For a wonderful change of pace, plan your Esther Manor vacation now -- unlimited fun and pleasure for the entire family! Indoor and outdoor swimming, steam rooms and health club, tennis, handball, golf, baseball, plus top entertainment, dancing and late, late shows await you. The Day Camp is under the alert supervision of trained counsellors. The Teenage Program is better than ever. Hospitality here is as warm and abundant as the rays of the sun. May we suggest that you plan your Esther Manor vacation now? Esther &amp; Irene
        </printedtext>
        <printedpubinfo side="b">
            Rt. 17B/Monticello, N.Y., 12701 Tel. (914) 794-7500 Direct Wire: (212) YU 9-3181
        </printedpubinfo>
        <writtentext/><date/>
    </postcard>
    <postcard n="4">
        <senderaddress side="b" name="Pte. Maynard A.T."/>
        <recipientaddress side="a" name="W.H. Caldwell Esq.">
            275 Clinton Ave., Brooklyn, N.Y. U.S.A.
        </recipientaddress>
        <printedheader side="a">
            We're all lit up - let battle commence
            This parcel has been presented by
        </printedheader>
        <printedtext side="b">
            Please write your message to the Donor below:-
            IMPORTANT: At the request of the authorities do not disclose any particulars of your unit
        </printedtext>
        <printedpubinfo side="a">
            Sketch by Grimes
        </printedpubinfo>
        <printedpubinfo side="b">
            This parcel is presented through the Over-Seas League Tobacco Fund.
        </printedpubinfo>
        <writtentext side="b">
            <date/>Dear Sir, Many thanks. I'll soon be out of here now, then I shall be lit up! God Bless America and F.D.R. Yours Sincerely, Pte. Maynard. A.T.
        </writtentext>
    </postcard>
    <postcard n="5">
        <senderaddress side="b" name="L.W. [unintelligible]">
            R # 1 Box 32 Webster, Mass.
        </senderaddress>
        <recipientaddress side="b" name="Mrs. F.G. Gopp">
            West Newsbury, Mass.
        </recipientaddress>
        <printedheader side="a">
            Woonsocket Falls and Sayles Street Bridge, Woonsocket, R.I.
        </printedheader>
        <printedtext/>
        <printedpubinfo side="b">
            The Leighton and Valentine Co.. N.Y. City. Printed in United States.
        </printedpubinfo>
        <writtentext side="b">
            <date/>River and bridges; I went visiting in this place last summer. Hope you will like the card and [unintelligible] soon.
        </writtentext>
    </postcard>
    <postcard n="6">
        <senderaddress/>
        <recipientaddress side="b" name="Miss Hall">
            Fern Lodge, Pueborough
        </recipientaddress>
        <printedheader side="a">
            Who are you?
        </printedheader>
        <printedheader side="b">
            Tuck's Post Card
        </printedheader>
        <printedtext side="b">
            If sent abroad, this space may only be used for name and address of sender.
        </printedtext>
        <printedpubinfo side="b">
            "Chicks and ducklings." Raphael Tuck &amp; Sons' "Oilette" [Regd.] Postcard 9175. Publishers to their majesties the king &amp; queen.
        </printedpubinfo>
        <writtentext side="a">
            Do you think you can find names for these?
        </writtentext>
        <writtentext side="b">
            <date/>Dear Nellie, Many thanks for P.G. Hope you are not all blown away. The weather has been fearful down here. I have been to five balls this week so you can guess I am nearly dead. Love it all, [unintelligible]
        </writtentext>
    </postcard>
    <postcard n="7">
        <senderaddress side="b" name="Douglas Gomery">
            4817 Drummond Ave., Chevy Chase, MD, 20815
        </senderaddress>
        <recipientaddress side="b" name="The Gomerys">
            1550 Highland Lane, Delray Beach, FL, 33444
        </recipientaddress>
        <printedheader side="a">
            R-6 Pagoda, Mt. Penn, Reading, Pa.
        </printedheader>
        <printedheader side="b">
            Pagoda
        </printedheader>
        <printedtext/>
        <printedpubinfo side="b">
            Reading, PA. 1908. 1939 view, Curt Teich Postcard Collection, Lake County (Ill.) Museum. From Ducks &amp; Diners © 1988 National Trust for Historic Preservation. The Preservation Press.
        </printedpubinfo>
        <writtentext side="b">
            <date>11/12/1992</date>What is a WONK? I don't really know -- a kind of expert in numbers. Puddles is better, Marilyn's ankle is better; but she had an emergency root canal yesterday UGH!
        </writtentext>
    </postcard>
</postcardexamples>


